parallel for Nelson Mandela as president prime ministers kings and queens friends Bose famous and not all gather here in South Africa has the world says goodbye
平行的纳尔逊·曼德拉总统总理国王和王后的朋友百色著名的，而不是所有聚集在这里，在南非拥有世界说再见
also the handshake seen around the world today the moments that has a lot of people talking to a massive search in the mountains of family missing for days in freezing temperatures has not been rescued in tonight there heroin stories
今天还看到了世界各地的握手，有很多人谈论到家庭中缺少的冻结温度的天山区大规模搜索的时刻尚未获救今晚有海洛因的故事
who was and businesses in the federal government tonight Meijer flight delays Philomath on the roads in there is another one on the way nightly news from South Africa begins now
谁是和企业在联邦政府今晚梅哲航班延误Philomath在那里的道路是另外一个来自南非的晚间新闻现在开始的方式
BC 19 News with Brian Williams reporting tonight from Pretoria South Africa
公元前19新闻与布赖恩·威廉斯从比勒陀利亚南​​非今晚报告
what has been a memorial like no other for a man like no other a heavy dose of celebration of fallen boisterous backdrop against a against which South Africa host of the world
什么一直没有像其他纪念一样，没有其他倒下的热闹背景下的庆祝对反对大剂量一个人，南非主办的世界
big name leaders from all over lead by four US presidents four British Prime Ministers assorted kings and celebrities a dictator or two and some surprises starting with heavy rain which kept the crowd size down here today
大牌领袖来自全国各地的主角由四位美国总统四名英国首相各类国王和名人一个或两个独裁者和一些惊喜开始今天不停的人群大小到这里大雨
mini instead had to watch on television inside while the mix of people who came to remember Nelson Mandela was extraordinary the kind of crowd he wants dreamed of the mix of politicians prove to be
迷你而是不得不在电视上观看，而里面的人谁组合来记住曼德拉是非凡的，他都想梦见政客的组合的这类人群被证明是
broad and what are the moments of the day came when President Obama found himself shaking hands with Raul Castro
广泛的，什么是一天的时刻来到时，美国总统奥巴马发现自己握手劳尔·卡斯特罗
brother of Fidel and the leader of Cuba it was that kind of a day n from here where Mandela's body will arrive shortly lie in state we go back south to the weather on NBC's Lester Holt to start a soft and I left her grave
卡斯特罗和古巴领导人是那种一个n天从这里哪里曼德拉的身体会到达的弟弟不久躺在状态，我们回去南方天气在NBC的莱斯特·霍尔特开始软，我离开了她的坟墓
Frank and powerful Tribute in Light Smith Nelson Mandela brought this country together in death be brought together an interesting collection of global allies and adversaries it was President Obama who drew the largest welcome
弗兰克和强大的Tribute在轻史密斯纳尔逊·曼德拉把这个国家一起死亡汇集全球的盟友和对手的一个有趣的收集是奥巴马总统谁画的最大的欢迎
4shared
互联星空，4Shared
and the world change some by motorcade entourages
和世界的车队随行人员改变一些
many more by foot
更多步行
Colby
科尔比
canvas at Nelson Mandela stitch together on East Joanie from activist to prisoner to President
帆布在纳尔逊·曼德拉在东琼妮缝合在一起从活动家囚犯总统
so much better
好多了
great grandchildren
曾孙
celebrate
庆祝
this was Mandela South Africa black and white 2 degrees in a crowd sometimes broken this song
这是曼德拉南非黑白2度在人群中，有时打破这首歌
Mandela's second wife Winnie embracing is with no one but Mandela could inspired this time
曼德拉的第二任妻子温妮拥抱是没有人，但曼德拉能激发这个时候
celebrities including Bono and actress Charlize Theron Mandela's partner in peace former South African president f.w de Klerk
名人波诺和女演员查理兹·塞隆曼德拉在和平南非前总统德克勒克伙伴
what are the days most remarkable images President Obama offering a polite handshake the Cuban dictator Raul Castro
什么是天最显着的图像奥巴马总统提供一个礼貌的握手古巴独裁者劳尔·卡斯特罗
the President Obama
总统奥巴马
the American presidency the command to crouch full attention
美国总统的命令蹲下充分重视
which three former President Jimmy Carter along with George Bush and Bill Clinton and their wives looking on
这三位前总统吉米·卡特以及乔治·布什和比尔·克林顿和他们的妻子在看
president recalled learning of Mandela struggle when she was a college student that's him sit on the right
主席回顾曼德拉的奋斗学习时，她是一名大学生就是他坐在右边
the others Eva Marcille
其他伊娃Marcille
continuous here tomorrow his body work and live in state for 3 days the family and Bips Brian will be first thing tomorrow morning
连续在这里明天他的身体工作和生活状态3天的家人和施虐者辅导计划布赖恩将是第一件事，明天早上
Lester Holt who was inside the stadium
莱斯特·霍尔特谁是球场内
for all of it as we said it was that kind of a get of the day on the other moment from today's memorial is getting some attention in Ida selfie
对于这一切，我们说这是一种从今天的追悼会其他时刻的一天一个get的是得到一些关注井田selfie
featuring President Obama British Prime Minister David Cameron and Danish Prime Minister Helle thorning-schmidt it instantly went viral guess it was designed to sing around the world in just minutes on the web
设有总统奥巴马，英​​国首相戴维·卡梅伦和丹麦首相赫勒托宁 - 施密特它瞬间爆红猜测它的目的是要唱世界各地的网络上只有几分钟的路程
how are special correspond to Charlene hunter Gault is with us here again tonight a veteran American journalist us live here for close to two decades you and I the distinguished task of covering this life you can hang it was a perfect African celebration
如何是特殊的对应夏琳猎人高尔特是我们在这里再次今晚一位资深的美国记者，我们在这里住了将近二十年你我覆盖这辈子你可以把它挂的杰出工作，是一个完美的庆祝非洲
Indian saw full on celebration going on behind the speakers what was it you think we witness
印度看到完整的庆祝活动将在扬声器背后到底是什么，你认为我们见证
well that's in the culture of South
那么这是在南方的文化
Dave Morin by celebrating because they believed that the body has not has departed but it has become an answer
戴夫·莫兰通过庆祝，因为他们相信，身体还没有已离开，但它已成为一个答案
and so they go to the grave to talk to the ancestors many of them still culturally a tune to that end help to get wisdom
所以他们进入阴间去跟祖先许多人仍然在文化曲子为此help来获取智慧
so its a celebration of life in a transition and death in the nature of how South African approach the transition
所以其生命的庆祝活动中如何南非的自然过渡和接近死亡的过渡
should be said this country pulled this off today and that's important it's been great Avenue Charlotte Madison breaking news from back home there's been a deal just announced on Capitol Hill in Washington
应该说这个国家今天拉这一关，这就是重要的它是伟大大道夏洛特麦迪逊打破从回家的消息有过刚刚宣布在国会山在华盛顿达成协议
boiled another government shutdown in early January Kelly O'Donnell on the hill tonight for us with details
煮今晚上详细的小山为我们的另一个政府关闭在月初凯利·奥唐奈
Washington dysfunction is on hold a bipartisan compromise was just an ounce open in running for 2 years it would also rollback some of the harshest automatic spending cuts sequester for the Pentagon a domestic programs
华盛顿功能障碍是保持两党妥协正好一盎司的开放运行了2年也将回滚一些最恶劣的自动削减开支的封存五角大楼国内节目
Reno Nevada taxes but you will pay new fees for airline travel and federal workers are being after contribute to their pension at this does not extend jobless benefits for those out of work the longest and still have to be passed but that's expected before Congress goes home for the holidays Brian
内华达州里诺税，但你将支付新的费用，航空旅行和政府工作人员正在后有助于在这个他们的退休金不会扩展为那些失去工作的失业救济金的时间最长，还是要通过，但该公司预计在国会回家的假期布莱恩
Kelly O'Donnell Capitol Hill in Washington with the late news from their Kelly thanks also tonight in Nevada and the desperate search for a missing family including for children has come to an end
凯利·奥唐奈国会山在华盛顿与他们的凯利感谢已故的消息也今晚在内华达州和绝望的寻找一个失踪的家庭，包括儿童已经走到了尽头
in the news here is good the family spend found alive and well after surviving since Sunday in subzero temperatures the discovery unfolded this afternoon about 90 miles outside Reno NBC's Miguel Almaguer has our story
在这里是个好消息家庭支出发现还活着后以及自上周日以来尚存在零下温度的发现展开今天下午90英里以外的雷诺NBC的米格尔Almaguer有我们的故事
Image S with mountains near Lovelock Nevada rescue team together for Thursday fearing they were running out of time
附近内华达州拉夫洛克救援队一起山上星期四担心他们的时间不多了图像S
temperatures 1400 last name
温度1400姓氏
the search for a family of 6 growing more desperate every hour James Glanton his girlfriend Christina mcIntee and 4 children ages 3 to 10 have been missing since Sunday
寻找一个6口之家变得越来越绝望每隔一小时詹姆斯Glanton女友克里斯蒂娜mcIntee和4个孩子3到10岁已经错过周日起
the family was headed for a day in the snow to rain is rugged remote in this time of the year it is zero temperatures temperatures can kill Crest Hill Banda hoe
家族为首每天在雪地里下雨是崎岖遥远在每年的这个时候是零下温度的温度可以杀死峦山锄班达亚齐
the family had a cell phone with the area Orion with remote there was no service still there last known signal help with search teams to a specific area
家庭拥有手机的猎户座区与偏远，没有服务仍然存在持续与知名搜索队到一个特定的区域信号帮助
National Guard launch helicopter in this morning what some call a miracle
在今天上午的国民警卫队直升机发射什么有人称之为奇迹
Chris Montez spotted the families overturned Jeep
克里斯·蒙特兹看准了家庭推翻吉普
they had a fire going in a whiskey rocks
他们有一个火要在一个威士忌的岩石
can a fire
能火
airlifted to a local hospital in entire community and family members heard the good news
空运到在整个社会和家庭成员在当地医院传来喜讯
Hollywood hits
好莱坞打
that's all
这是所有
the family of 6 in good condition after a Sunday Drive to play in the snow
6一个星期天驱动器后，家庭条件不错在雪地里玩
don't ever forget
永远不要忘记
Miguel Almaguer NBC News Los Angeles
米格尔Almaguer NBC新闻洛杉矶
process women covering so far this week the East Coast has been dealing with its own blast of literary weather today the good news was the storm any were
流程女性本周涵盖至今东海岸今天已经处理了自己的文学爆炸天气的好消息是暴风雨任何人
morning wasn't quite as hard as first forecast know it still manage to stop a lot of people in their tracks especially in the nation's capital
早晨是不太硬如首次预测知道它仍然设法阻止了很多人在他们的踪迹尤其是在国家的首都
which is where Tom Costello is for us again tonight
这就是汤姆·科斯特洛是我们今晚再次
hibriten the federal government area schools closed today we still got several thousand people in neighboring states without power on a very cold night Meijer flight descriptions and 1400 cancellations and Counting
hibriten联邦政府地区的学校今日停课，我们仍然有几千人在邻国没有权力在一个非常寒冷的夜晚梅哲飞行说明和1400取消和计数
daybreak Road Altadena
黎明路阿塔狄纳
cancellations is going to be another rescheduling an early cancellation it all seems to be due to the weather Big delays in the Northeast
取消将是另一个重新安排的提早取消这一切似乎是由于东北天气大延误
Kennesaw yellow in Washington Australian students McAllen see the plane slave
肯尼索黄色在华盛顿澳大利亚学生麦卡伦看到飞机从机
fender bender
车祸
accidents today was more about a few inches of snow
今天的事故是更多了几英寸的积雪
its a first night snow for 2 years we haven't had no hair
它的第一夜雪2年我们没有均无毛
perfect Tuesday in DC Thomas and sister
完美周二在直流托马斯和妹妹
Mike Roussell sweating days are long over
迈克Roussell出汗的日子早已过去
Kentucky to snow
肯德基雪
blue skies the weather channels Mike Seidel warmed up storm number 3
晴空万里的天气频道迈克赛德尔回暖风暴3号
PC Philadelphia New York it's mostly rain maybe some ice early on Boston what have a little bit of everything the ski resorts lot of snow
电脑费城纽约它主要下雨也许有些冰早就波士顿什么都有了一点点的滑雪场很大的雪
what to use to season
使用季节什么
who's the season waiting for no reason
谁是本赛季的等待没有理由
it's all in the attitude Tom Costello NBC News Washington
这一切都在态度汤姆·科斯特洛NBC新闻华盛顿
and big news from one of the Detroit Big Three automakers a history making out tonight from General Motors naming the first woman
从底特律三巨头的一大新闻汽车的历史使得今晚从通用汽车命名的第一个女人
CEO ever to run a global auto maker Mary Barra is a 33 year GM
首席执行官曾运行一个全球性的汽车制造商玛丽巴拉是33年通用汽车
veteran daughter of a GM assembly part maker she started there is an intern
通用汽车装配部分制造商，她开始有老将的女儿是一名实习生
Rose all the way up through the ranks as an engineer to become the company's product development Chick fil A have for us tonight taking action a year
通过等级的工程师玫瑰一路攀升，成为该公司的产品开发小鸡FIL一个已经为我们今晚采取行动一年
the Newtown parents who lost their children that day talk about a big move to tackle the mental health crisis in our country and later
在新城的父母谁失去了他们的孩子，每天谈论的一大举措，以解决我国的心理健康危机和后
porting a huge surprise upon landing for a plain lo folla Paso
对于一个普通的卤味folla埃尔帕索移植后登陆一个巨大的惊喜
back home in the US this Saturday Walmart in one year since the awful school shooting in Newtown Connecticut since then
回到家里，在美国这个星期六沃尔玛一年，因为在Newtown康涅狄格可怕的校园枪击案此后
growing attention given to a link in some cases between violence and mental illness today Vice President Joe Biden join where is Newtown families Lupin pleading for more help along these lines and some of them spoke with our NBC News national correspondent Kate snow
今天给一个链接，暴力和精神病之间有一些情况下，副总统拜登加入越来越多的关注，其中是现代城家庭鲁邦恳求沿着这些路线更多的帮助和他们中的一些采访了我们的NBC新闻国家通讯员凯特雪
the government shut down for a snow day for parents of three children who died in Newtown last year was too important to miss
政府关闭了一个大雪天的三个孩子谁在Newtown去年去世的父母太重要了，错过
the dialogue on mental health has been lacking over a long period of time in and we really need to do to change the the focus tell me how we can prevent violence and aggression as opposed to reacting to it
对心理健康的对话一直缺乏在一段时间的长期，我们真正需要做改变的重点告诉我如何才能防止暴力和侵略，而不是被动应付
when Jereme Richmond and his wife lost her daughter Iviona to sign to start a foundation dedicated to brain research for decades predictive claimed huge gap between the number of Americans who need mental health care and access to that care
当Jereme里士满和他的妻子失去了她的女儿Iviona签署开始致力于大脑研究了几十年的预测称的美国人谁需要心理保健和访问该照顾的数量之间存在着巨大的差距的基础
during the recession state budget
经济衰退的国家预算中
Newtown stat least 37 States has increased spending on mental health programs today the federal government stepped up to which vice president died in an ounce in 100 million dollars to help community health centers across the country established expand behavioral health services
现代城统计至少有37个国家已就精神卫生计划今日增加的支出，联邦政府加紧其副总裁一盎司死了100万美元，以帮助全国各地的社区卫生服务中心建立了扩展行为健康服务
and you improve mental health access in rural areas
你改善农村地区的精神卫生接入
this is a very important
这是一个非常重要的
we still have a long way to go with a drop in the ocean but
我们还有很长的路要走，在大海里的一滴水，但
its progress report released 2 weeks ago concluded Newtown shooter Adam Lanza had significant mental health issues you refuse treatment what contribution to the shootings if any is unknown the report said
其发布的2个星期前进度报告的结论现代城射手亚当·兰扎有你拒绝治疗显著心理健康问题的报告中说什么贡献枪击案如有不明
Scarlett Lewis Tucson jesse was killed at Sandy Hook Elementary Toshiba leaves what happened to Ben prevented with better mental health care
斯嘉丽·刘易斯图森杰西是在桑迪胡克小学东芝杀死叶发生了什么事，以防止奔更好的精神卫生保健
tragedy started with an angry god and Adams have you didn't have the tools to know how
悲剧开始了愤怒的上帝和亚当斯你有没有知道的工具如何
handle that starting conversations is one of the Weasleys Families what America honor their children
处理这起谈话是韦斯莱家族什么美国兑现自己的孩子之一
starts with an R home and it starts with an R Kennedy
开始与R家，并将它与一个R肯尼迪开始
so many Newtown families have told me they hope this is just the beginning politically mental health care may be easier to change than gun laws but it also like to see change their 2 despite all the cause for change after Newtown it's worth noting that has been 16 more school shootings since then
这么多的新城镇家庭都告诉我，他们希望这仅仅是个开始政治精神卫生保健可能是更容易改变比枪支法，但它也希望看到改变自己2，尽管所有的原因变更后现代城这是值得注意的是，已经16更多校园枪击此后
Kate snow back in a New York studios tonight thanks for your reporting and we're back in a moment will the new message on a photo we received from high above today
凯特雪早在纽约的工作室，今晚感谢您的报告，我们又回到了一会儿将在我们从接到高今日上方照片的新信息
the founder and chairman of Lululemon has resigned forced out of the job running the company he started because of remarks email about their own customers that did not go over well
Lululemon公司的创办人兼主席已被迫辞职，因为电子邮件的言论对自己的客户，没有去很好跑出来的公司，他开始工作
Lululemon as you may know makes high and yoga wear among other things they have a loyal customer base men and women
Lululemon的你可知道让他们之间有一个忠诚的客户群男人和女人其他的东西高，瑜珈服
but that was so early test in one hour former CEO chip Wilson said some women's bodies don't work for yoga pants the company had earlier compound of injury blaming a problem with see through yoga pants instructed Ali anatomies of some of the women buying
但是这是如此早期的测试在一小时前CEO芯片威尔逊说，一些女性的身体没有为瑜伽裤该公司早些时候曾指责伤害的问题化合物与识破瑜伽裤的一些妇女责成阿里解剖购买工作
you may Ricola while back we ask the International Space Station for helping taking a picture of a house in Australia with you
你可能利口乐前阵子我们要求国际空间站，帮助采取的房子在澳洲的图片与您
current record holder for Christmas lights we figured it would be visible from space sell we out the professionals the good news is they have
目前的纪录保持者为圣诞灯饰，我们估计这将是从太空可见卖了我们的专业人士的好消息是他们有
found the neighborhood in question during the daytime orbit overhead and we are hoping now there night time travels well soon show it and its full wattage on Christmas glory or thanks to our orbiting photography department for taking me occasional request
发现有问题的邻居白天轨道开销时，我们希望现在有夜间井游记很快表现出来，并充分发挥其功率在圣诞节荣耀还是感谢我们的轨道摄影系带我偶尔要求
Time magazine still does a great job drumming up in trust for is oldest franchise Person of the Year someone who has for better or worse have the most impact on the world and the news
时代杂志还做了伟大的工作，宣达以信托形式为年度谁的人有或好或坏，对世界上最古老的冲击专营人士和新闻
this past year case in point tonight they have told us of the 5 finalist names the editors are considering they are in no particular order NSA leaker Edward Snowden Syrian president pasar Assad Edith Windsor who challenge
在过去的一年例证今晚他们告诉的5名入围我们的编辑们考虑到他们是在没有特定的顺序国家安全局泄密者爱德华·斯诺登叙利亚总统阿萨德巴刹伊迪丝·温莎谁挑战
fence of Marriage Act in one of the Supreme Court Texas senator Ted Cruz and the new pope Francis Person of the Year will be announce live tomorrow morning on today
婚姻法案在最高法院德州参议员特德·克鲁兹和年度的新教皇弗朗西斯人物之一栅栏将现场宣布明早今天
the other way you can make news with something blatantly promotional use if it's a really good heartwarming idea
你可以让新闻的东西公然宣传用的，如果它是一个非常好的主意温馨的另一种方式
well the Canadian based airline WestJet setup 19 hidden cameras and one of Santa's helpers non traditional blue so it would be confused for the real Santa they were on hands as travelers young and old
以及加拿大的航空公司WestJet的设置19隐藏的相机和一个圣诞老人的助手非传统的蓝色所以它会被混淆了真正的圣诞老人，他们的双手为旅客老幼
what they wanted for Christmas this year from trains to dollars to flat screen TVs and smartphones wild
今年他们想要的圣诞节从列车美元，平板电视和智能手机的野生
flight was in the air over Canada
飞行在空中超过加拿大
the airline with lots of Santa's helpers
有很多圣诞老人的助手航空公司
arrange for the 250 gifts to beatbox wrapped around the baggage carousel where they were greeted and open
安排250礼品口技缠在行李传送带那里迎接他们的是开放的
passengers none more stoned in the man who didn't take the Santas helper seriously and ask her underwear which is what he got all the wildest thing is now a television commercial
乘客在男人谁没有采取圣诞老人助手认真，问她的内衣，而这正是他把所有的最疯狂的事情是现在电视广告没有更多砸死
what they do get points for Christmas spirit when we come back from South Africa
他们做了什么得到的圣诞精神点，我们回来的时候从南非
the place where Nelson Mandela became a symbol of hope
曼德拉成为希望的象征的地方
finally from South Africa tonight we took a moment this afternoon wall the memorial gathering was still going on but winding down to walk through Soweto just as a way of gauging life
终于从南非今晚我们花了一点时间下午墙纪念馆集会仍在进行，但蜿蜒而下穿过索韦托走路就像衡量一种生活方式
in a specific part of this country right now how its changed where it might be headed especially in light of the loss of limb and they consider a hero
在这个国家的一个特定部分，现在怎么样了改变，它可能尤其是在肢体丧失的领导和他们认为的英雄
this is the South Africa Nelson Mandela identified with a privately claim him as one of their own
这是南非的曼德拉确定了一个私下声称他是他们中的一
so
what you told me you live forever
你告诉我，你永远活着
walking around Soweto you can witness the gamut of human experience
走在索韦托你可以亲眼目睹人类经验的色域
what comes with think you very much
什么自带很想你
after 20 years of coming here there were visible changes on this trip in this neighborhood a slight UPTET in the standard of living in happiness and empowerment but its hard to see anything else in the midst of that old familiar grinding Alberti
经过20年来这里的有在这附近有明显的变化，此行生活在幸福和授权的标准略有UPTET但其很难看到任何东西在熟悉的老磨阿尔贝蒂之中
send you to hell
送你下地狱
because death is viewed as a transition because even today's rain is seen as a blessing from Mandela's passage its perfectly consist of the people in morning or also happy im celebrated
因为死亡被视为一个过渡，因为即使在今天的雨水被看作是从曼德拉才通过的祝福它完全由人们在早晨或也庆祝快乐的IM
hearing to me
听我的
and I love you
我爱你
are you are you proud of the world has come here today
你是你的世界的骄傲今天来到这里
727 prison
727监狱
the man I first met 20 years ago was the newly elected president back when we were both much younger is being held as their George Washington there Gundy there Lincoln their mother Teresa there Dr King in their FDR all rolled into one
我第一次见到20年前的人是新当选的总统回来时，我们都年轻了许多被关押他们的乔治·华盛顿有范甘迪有林肯的母亲特里萨有金博士在罗斯福都集于一身
Nelson Mandela wanted a country where babies were born into freedom and equality of the two if the qualities that for so many remains a long walk
纳尔逊·曼德拉希望在那里婴儿出生成为自由和两个平等的国家，如果品质，对于这么多的仍然是一个很长的步行
which brings us to tonight after a day of heavy rain tonights fog has blotted out the Union Buildings behind us but beginning in a few hours this is where Nelson Mandela will come to lie in state as the long farewell Continues right up till
这大雨一整天后，给我们带来了今晚今晚的雾已经遮住了联合大厦在我们后面，但在开始的几个小时，这是曼德拉将来到在于国家作为长期的告别继续向右直至
burial next Sunday that is for us are broadcast on a Tuesday night thank you for being here with us I'm Brian Williams reporting tonight from Pretoria South Africa
葬下周日也就是我们正在播出的一个星期二晚上谢谢你能在这里和我们我布赖恩·威廉斯，今晚从比勒陀利亚南​​非的报告
help to see you from are New York studios for tomorrow a good night
帮忙看看你是纽约的工作室明天一个美好的夜晚